Guide to the Ted Fagan Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Reel to reel tapes
  - Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.) Intermissions II, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1010)
    Piano Round Table -- Masiello, Alberta on Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Otello -- Interview with Pavarotti, Luciano -- Horne, Marilyn, mezzo-soprano; Sutherland, Joan, 1926-, soprano. Rehearsal. Bonynge, Richard, conductor, Oct. 15, 1979.
  - Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.) Intermissions 1983, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1011)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Messa da Requiem Feb. 20, 1982, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1012)
    Horne, Marilyn, mezzo-soprano; Price, Leontyne, soprano; Domingo, Plácido, 1941-, tenor
  - Recital. Rostropovich, Mstislav, 1927-, cello; Vishnevskaya, Galinas soprano, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1013)
    Washington, D.C.
  - Plaisir des Dieux, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1014)
    Petite Anthologie des chansons de la Salle de Garde - Specialment interpretées commes en salle de garde par un Tonus des Hôpitaux Parisiens
  - Sills, Beverly, soprano, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1015)
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Quintets, piano, violin, viola, violoncello, double bass, D. 667, A major, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1016)
    TV simulcast. Barenboim, Daniel, 1942-, piano; Du Pré, Jacqueline, 1945-1987, cello; Perlman, Itzhak, 1945-, violin; Mehta, Zubin
  - Opera selections, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1017)
  - Sopranos, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1018)
  - Contraltos and Mezzo-Sopranos, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1019)
  - Caruso, Enrico, 1873-1921, tenor, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1020)
    Neapolitan song. Manella mia -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Pêcheurs de perles. Selection; Arlésienne. Intermezzo; arr. -- Bellini, Vincenzo, 1801-1835. Neapolitan song -- Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883. Martha. Selection
  - Voices from the Past, 7" reel (Box 43, Folder 1021)
    From the BBC's treasury of recorded productions. John, Augustus, 1878-1961, painter -- Moore, Henry, 1898-1986, sculptor -- Beecham, Thomas, Sir, 1879-1961, conductor -- Evans, Edith, Dame, 1888-1976, actress -- Tempest, Marie, 1866-1942, singer, actress -- Smythe, Ethel, composer and a leader of the women's suffrage movement.
  - Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Moses und Aron, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1022)
  - Rigaux, Henri, comedian, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1023)
  - Miscellaneous vocal selections, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1024)
  - Interviews, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1025)
    Interview with Mulhare, Edward Jan. 27, 1959 -- Leonard, Bill interviews Fagan, Ted: on being an interpretaer at the UN (ca.1960) -- Turner, Eva (see tape 65)
  - Miscellaneous vocal selections, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1026)
  - Miscellaneous vocal selections, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1027)
  - Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.) Intermissions April, 11, 1977, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1028)
  - San Francisco Opera Broadcast, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1029)
    Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. Act I -- Various vocal recordings
  - Miscellaneous vocal selections, 7" reel (Box 44, Folder 1030)
  - Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.) Auditions March 1980, 5" reel (Box 44, Folder 1031)
  - A Man around the house, 5" reel (Box 44, Folder 1032)
    Sound effects
  - Queen Elizabeth's Address at the XII Assembly of the United Nations, 5" reel (Box 44, Folder 1033)
  - Fagan's index cards to the reel to reel tapes (Box 45)
- Discs
  - Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Ballads. Dec. 5, 1963, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Byron, George. Theme and Jingle June 25, 1946, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1867-1957 - Rehearsal, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bloch, Ernest, 1880-1959. Schelomo, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Nelsova, Zara, cello. Prague 1960
  - Vauxhall Gardens Concert 1851, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Concerto, piano, no. 1, op. 23, B? minor. Jan. 12, 1953, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Horowitz, Vladimir, 1903-1989, piano; Szell, George, 1897-1970, conductor
  - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Werther. Act I 1952, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Werther. Act II and III 1952, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Werther. Act III 1952, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Schumann, Elisabeth, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Nacht und Träume; Seligkeit; Einsamkeit, D. 620
  - Schumann, Elisabeth, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Nähe des Geliebten; Lachen und Weinen; Wiegenlied, D. 304; Schmetterling
  - Schumann, Elisabeth, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Jüngling an der Quelle; Geheimes; Ständchen, D. 889
  - Schumann, Elisabeth, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Loreley [sic]; Ständchen, D. 635; An die Nachtigall, D. 497; Liebhaber in allen Gestalten
  - Schumann, Elisabeth, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Gretchen am Spinnrade; Musensohn
  - Bishop, Frank Nov. 9, 1946, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787. Alceste (1767). Caprice -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Fantasien, harpsichord, BWV 903a, D minor.
  - Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Rondo à capriccio, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Orchestration by Kuphal, Fred
  - Sharp, Sidney and Sharp, Jeanette, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 10 in. (Palmidic acid problem) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Wieniawski, Henri, 1835-1880. Romance sans paroles et Rondo élégant -- Gershwin, George, 1898-1937. Goldwyn follies. Love is here to stay -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Thaïs. Méditation -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Jahreszeiten. Winter
  - Professor's Birthday. May 28, 1954, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    An operetta in one act presented to Prof. Bloomfield, Arthur L. in the Treasure Island Naval Training Station Officer's Club.
  - McCormack, John, 1884-1945 Commemorative Record to the reviewers on the 10th anniversary of his death Sept. 16, 1955, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Christus am Ölberge. Selections
  - Jingle Bells and Noel and Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809 Caisson [sic]Christmas 1950, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Whitsell, Leon O., b. 1876, singer
  - Christmas CarolsChristmas 1951, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (preservation needed) (Box 4, Folder 21)
    by Leon and George
  - Johnston & Busher wish you a Merry Chrsitmas, 1 sound disc: shellac; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Johnston & Busher, singers. Palestrina, Giovanni Pierluigi da, 1525?-1594. O bone Jesu, miserere -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Choräle von verschiedener Art, BWV 651-668. Allein Gott in der Höh' sei Ehr', BWV 662 -- French Carol. Angels o'er the fields -- English Carol. Boar's head carol
  - Shaw, Artie, 1910-2004, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    September Song -- Little Jazz
  - Sinatra, Frank, 1915-1998 and Stafford. Ballads -- Shavers, Charlie, 1917-1971. Laguna Leap Sept. 28, 1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Miller, Glenn, 1904-1944 Dec.31, 1941, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Radio recording of Miller, Glenn, 1904-1944, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Miller, Glenn, 1904-1944, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    A chip off the old block -- Keep 'em flying
  - Miller, Glenn, 1904-1944, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Boulder Buff -- Flagenauer
  - Miller, Glenn, 1904-1944, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Old assembly line -- Measure for measure
  - Miller, Glenn, 1904-1944, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Oh so good! -- Intermetso
  - Barnet, Charlie Oct. 5, 1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Redskin Rhumba -- Layden with music
  - Vivanco, Moisés and Sumac, Yma, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Conjunto Folklórico Peruano. Amor Indio -- Inka Son -- Benita.
  - Presidio Junior High School, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Instrumental and vocal groups. Miller, Glenn, 1904-1944, director. Dance Band -- Steve Barrie Combo -- Kings -- Sharps
  - White, Roderick. Negro Chant, 1 sound disc: shellac; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - A special recording of Lili Marlene. With the compliments of Time. The weekly newsmagazine.April 29, 1943, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Soldier's song of both the Axis and the Allies overseas
  - United Nations' unique records to aid the world's refugees. All star festival, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Armstrong, Louis, 1901-1971; Chevalier, Maurice, 1888-1972; Cole, Nat King, 1917-1965; Crosby, Bing, 1903-1977; Day, Doris, 1924-; Fitzgerald, Ella; Jackson, Mahalia, 1911-1972; Mouskouri, Nana; Page, Patti; Paraná, Luis Alberto del, 1926-; Piaf, Edith, 1915-1963; Shelton, Anne; Valente, Caterina, 1931-
  - African Music Research, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Palmitic acid problem) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Patkeeff, George and his Russian Cavalry Bandca. 1959, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Palmitic acid problem) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Not labeled, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Acetate layer peeling) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Record of "Speeches" by our enemy by Robbio [sic] -- Miller, Glenn, 1904-1944. Swing low sweet chariot, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Palmitic acid problem) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Marina. Montilla Rec. I, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Fungus problem) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Marina. Montilla Rec. II, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Barry, John IV, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Panel Discussion, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Southern Comfort Promo, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Leon's Christmas recordDec. 1949, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - For Sandy Calder's 75th birthdayJuly 22, 1973, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 7 in. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Rock n' roll, Country, Swing, Big Band, Boogiewoogy, 1 sound disc: vinyl; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Solo piano music from the Romantic repertoire, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Roger, Suzane; Teacher of Louise [notes from dust jacket]
  - Rayner, Sydney, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Popular songs, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Fungus problem) (Box 4, Folder 51)
    James, H. Two o' clock jump. Aug. 7, 1943 -- Forest, H, and James, H. You'll never know. Sept. 2, 1943
  - Patkeeff, George and his Russian Cavalry BandJune 28, 1957, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Palmitic acid problem) (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Parade march of the Kirasir Guards
  - Not labeled, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 53)
    Originally in the same sleeve as Disc 52
  - American folk songs and spiritualsJune, 1945, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 54)
    Lind
  - Radio broadcast: What is Bop?, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Regional economics speech, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 58)
    Arias from diverse seldom played operas (continuation, see rec.15 a)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Madrigals, book 6. Lagrime d'amante al sepolcro dell'amata Dec. 29, 1949, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 60)
    Library of Laski, Leon. Station: ABF
  - Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Madrigals, book 6. Lagrime d'amante al sepolcro dell'amata Dec. 29, 1949, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Elektra, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 62)
    Varnay, Astrid, soprano; Nikolaidi, Elena, 1909-, mezzo-soprano; New York Philharmonic. Mitropoulos, Dimitri, 1896-1960, conductor
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Elektra, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Elektra, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Elektra, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Library of Laski, Leon. Station: ABFJan. 12, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 66)
    Menuhin, Yehudi, 1916-1999, violin; Menuhin, Hephzibah, 1920-1981, piano. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sonatas, violin, piano, K. 376, F major -- Morley, Thomas, 1557-1603? Balletts. My bonny lasse shee smyleth -- Trad. Sumer is icumin in -- Morley, Thomas, 1557-1603? Balletts. Now is the month of maying -- Byrd, William, 1542 or 3-1623. Songs of sundrie natures. I thought that Love had been a boy -- Leroy, flute; Pessl, Yella, 1906-, harpsichord. Leonardo, da Vinci, 1452-1519. Sonata flute, harpsichord, D Major -- Milstein, Nathan, 1903-1992, violin. Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Sonatas, violin, continuo, F. XIII, 12, A major -- Rameau, Jean Philippe, 1683-1764. Pièces de clavecin en concerts. No 5. Cupis; Tambourins -- Boccherini, Luigi, 1743-1805. Quartets, strings, G minor
  - Library of Laski, Leon. Station: ABFJan. 12, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung. Act I Jan. 8, 1950, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung. Act I Jan. 8, 1950, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung. Act II Jan. 8, 1950, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung. Act II Jan. 8, 1950, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung. Act II Jan. 8, 1950, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schöne Müllerin Jan. 6, 1950, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 73)
    ABF station. Lehmann, Lotte, singer
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schöne Müllerin Jan. 6, 1950, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - An hour with Bach. Radio Program. ABFFeb. 1, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    Landowska, Wanda, piano. Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Französische Suiten. Nr. 6; Greene, Eric, tenor. Matthäuspassion. Selection; Osborne, Ellen, soprano. Herr Jesu Christ, wahr' Mensch und Gott (Cantata). Seele ruht in Jesu Händen; Liebster Gott, wenn werd ich sterben. Doch weichet, ihr tollen vergeblichen Sorgen; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Partita, no. 3; Sonatas, violin in E and C.
  - An hour with Bach. Radio Program. ABFFeb. 1, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787. Orphée et Eurydice Jan. 22, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 77)
    Ferrier, Kathleen, 1912-1953, soprano. Vlachopoulos, Zoë, 1916-, soprano. Glyndebourne Festival Chorus. Southern Philharmonic Orchestra. Stiedry, Fritz, conductor.
  - Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787. Orphée et Eurydice Jan. 22, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 78)
    Ferrier, Kathleen, 1912-1953, contralto. Vlachopoulos, Zoë, 1916-, soprano. Glyndebourne Festival Chorus. Southern Philharmonic Orchestra. Stiedry, Fritz, conductor.
  - Opera concert. Radio program. ABF station.Jan. 23, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 79)
    Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Hamlet. Caruso, Enrico, 1873-1921, tenor; Ruffo, Titta, 1877-1953, baritone -- Galli-Curci, Amelita, 1882-1963, soprano; Melba, Nellie, Dame, 1861-1931, soprano.
  - Opera concert. Radio program. ABF station.Jan. 23, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Oedipus Rex Jan. 15, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 81)
    ABF station.
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Oedipus Rex Jan. 15, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Oedipus Rex Jan. 15, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Records to live with. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 2, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 3, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 85)
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Cassations, K. 99, B? major; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Mass, K. 66, C major. Spiritum Sanctum; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Quartets, strings, K. 80, G major; Contredanses, K. 123, B? major; Regina Coeli, K. 108, C major; Vesperae de Dominica. De profundis. K. 93; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Symphony, K. 112, F major; Sonata, organ, K. 144, D major; Sonata, organ, K. 145, F major; Divertimento, K. 136, D major; Divertimento, K. 138, F major
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 3, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 3, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 3, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 89)
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. [works not specified]
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF stationFeb. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Great moments in opera. Radio program. ABF station. From the library of Migliorini, LouisFeb. 6, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 95)
    Originally presented at the Philadelphia Academy in 1914. Caruso, Enrico, 1873-1921, tenor. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Selections. Celeste Aïda; Gadski, Johanna, 1872-1932, soprano. Ritorna vincitor; Homer, Louise, 1871-1947, contralto. Fu la sorte dell'armi; Amato, Pasquale, baritone and Gadski, Johanna, 1872-1932, soprano O patria mia
  - Liturgical Music. Radio program. ABF station. Feb. 11, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 96)
    Shaw, Robert, 1916-1999, conductor. Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Choräle von verschiedener Art, BWV 645-650. Wachet auf, ruft uns die Stimme; Paris Philharmonic Chorus and orchestra. Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Masses, BWV 233-236
  - Liturgical Music. Radio program. ABF station. Feb. 11, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 3, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 98)
    Wiener Philharmoniker. Walter, Bruno, 1876-1962, conductor. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Finta giardiniera. Overture; Reichelt, Elisabeth, 1910-2001, soprano. Seidler, Karoline, soprano. Winkler, Hermann, tenor. Geme la tortorella; Ludwig. Ah dal pianto, dal singhiozzo; Sonatas, piano, K. 189g, E? major; Sonatas, piano, K. 282, E? major; Schwarzkopf, Elisabeth, soprano. Wiener Philharmoniker. Re pastore. L'amerò, sarò costante; Birmingham Orchestra. Cameron, Basil, 1884-1975, conductor Finta giardiniera. Noi donne poverine; Sonatas, piano, K. 283, G major; Bassoon and cello. K. 292; Missa brevis, K. 115
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 3, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 3, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 101)
    Menuhin, Yehudi, 1916-1999, violin. Enesco, Georges, 1881-1955, conductor. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Concerto, violin, K. 216, G major; Beecham, Thomas, Sir, 1879-1961, conductor. Nozze di Figaro. Overture; Szigeti, Joseph, 1892-1973, violin. Beecham, Thomas, Sir, 1879-1961, conductor. Concerto, violin, K. 218, D major; Leipzig Gewandhaus Quintet. Divertimento No. 8; Heifetz, Jascha, 1901-1987, violin. Barbirolli, John, Sir, 1899-1970, conductor. Concerto, violin, K. 218, D major.
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 10, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 24, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 104)
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Finta giardiniera
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 24, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 24, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 24, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Mozart Cycle. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 24, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Survey of Music. Radio program. WABF station. Apr. 2, 1950, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 109)
    Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974. Suite d'après Corrette -- Wyschnegradsky, Ivan, 1893-1979. Ainsi parlait Zarathoustra -- Lefebre. Gallon. Cadence et divertissement for clarinet and orchestra.
  - Welsh Chorale. Radio program. ABF station. Apr. 2, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 110)
    Victoria, Tomás Luis de, ca. 1548-1611. Motets (1572). Vere languores nostros -- Gregorian Chant. Christus Factus Est -- Palestrina, Giovanni Pierluigi da, 1525?-1594. Masses, book 12. Missa Ascendo ad Patrem -- Gregorian Chant.. Victimae Paschali Laudes -- Byrd, William, 1542 or 3-1623. Haec dies -- Grechaninov, Alexander Tikhonovich. Cherubic Hymn
  - Mozart Cycled. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 17, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 111)
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Concerto, bassoon, K, 230 a B? major; arr; Serenades, K. 239, D major; Concertos, 3 pianos, K. 242, F major.
  - Mozart Cycled. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 17, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Mozart Cycled. Radio program. ABF station. Mar. 17, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Great Moments in Opera. Radio program. ABF station. From the library of Migliorini, LouisApr. 17, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 114)
    Garden, Mary, 1874-1967, soprano. Ruffo, Titta, 1877-1953, baritone. Heldy, Fanny, 1888-1973, soprano. Luart, Emma,soprano. Farrar, Geraldine, 1882-1967, soprano. Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Thaïs.
  - Great Moments in Opera. Radio program. ABF station. From the library of Migliorini, LouisApr. 17, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Rrecords to live with. Radio program. ABF station. Apr. 6, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 116)
    Rampal, Jean Pierre, flute. Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonatas, flute, harpsichord, BWV 1030, B minor -- Rothwell, Evelyn, oboe. Corelli, Arcangelo, 1653-1713. Sonatas, violin, continuo, op. 5. Selections; arr. -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concertos, violoncello (2), C major -- Schwarzkopf, Elisabeth, soprano. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Exsultate, jubilate
  - Rrecords to live with. Radio program. ABF station. Apr. 6, 1 sound disc: soundsheet; 7 in. (Box 5, Folder 117)